<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fixed on Tactically Creative</title>
    <link>http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/fixed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fixed on Tactically Creative</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:42:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/fixed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Along with &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ford_Prefect_(character)&#34;&gt;Ford Prefect&lt;/a&gt;, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a &lt;em&gt;hyperspace bypass&lt;/em&gt;. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He rather enjoys tea, but seems to have trouble obtaining it in the far reaches of the galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In time, he learns how to fly and carves a niche for himself as a sandwich-maker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//placehold.it/300x300&#34; class=&#34;profile&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tactically-creative.co.uk/projects/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy is a comedy science fiction series created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Douglas_Adams&#34;&gt;Douglas Adams&lt;/a&gt;. Originally a radio comedy broadcast on BBC Radio 4 in 1978, it was later adapted to other formats, and over several years it gradually became an international multi-media phenomenon. Adaptations have included stage shows, a &amp;ldquo;trilogy&amp;rdquo; of five books published between 1979 and 1992, a sixth novel penned by &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eoin_Colfer&#34;&gt;Eoin Colfer&lt;/a&gt; in 2009, a 1981 TV series, a 1984 computer game, and three series of three-part comic book adaptations of the first three novels published by DC Comics between 1993 and 1996. There were also two series of towels, produced by Beer-Davies, that are considered by some fans to be an &amp;ldquo;official version&amp;rdquo; of The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy, as they include text from the first novel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;movie&#34;&gt;Movie&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Hollywood-funded film version, produced and filmed in the UK, was released in April 2005, and radio adaptations of the third, fourth, and fifth novels were broadcast from 2004 to 2005. Adams did many of these adaptations, including the novels, the TV series, the computer game, and the earliest drafts of the Hollywood film’s screenplay, and some of the stage shows introduced new material written by Adams.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>